<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Holidays on Andrew and Laura</title>
    <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Holidays on Andrew and Laura</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Singapore and Thailand</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2018singaporethailand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2018singaporethailand/</guid>
      <description>Friday 22nd June 5.30am left home for Gatwick for 14 hour flight to Singapore!
Saturday 23rd June Landed Singapore 6.30am Singapore time &amp;amp; taxi to Scarlet Hotel to leave luggage until check in time at 2pm. Both totally knackered, but our room is not free. Wandered down to Food Street &amp;amp; found the Old Coffee Shop for iced coffee &amp;amp; a cig. No smoking allowed in most areas here. Had a walk around town &amp;amp; had lunch at the Manchurian restaurant in Food Street later on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Mojacar Fiesta</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2018mojacarfiesta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2018mojacarfiesta/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 5th June Pete collected me at 9.45am to take me to Heathrow airport where I am meeting Jac &amp;amp; flying out to Mojacar for the Christians &amp;amp; Moors Fiesta.
We met up just outside the airport &amp;amp; grabbed a coffee &amp;amp; had a last cigarette before checking in. We wandered around the duty free &amp;amp; I bought some Clinique moisture surge face cream as the sample felt so good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Croatia for Laura&#39;s 60th Birthday</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2016croatia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2016croatia/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 25th June Lunch at the Royal Thai with Grahame, then home to sort out last minute bits before Peter arrived to take us to Luton airport for our flight to Dubrovnik. Lots of traffic, but Peter thankfully knows the back roads &amp;amp; got us there on time. Delays on flight so hung around a lot. Eventually set off over 2 hours later &amp;amp; arrived at ten to midnight. Cleared customs very quickly &amp;amp; I collected luggage whilst Andrew sorted out the hire car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Amsterdam Long Weekend</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2016amsterdam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2016amsterdam/</guid>
      <description>Friday 22nd April Set off at 12.30 to drive to Canterbury to stay overnight at The Millers Arms. Accident en route so miles of tail back, my journey took over 5 hours instead of 2 1&amp;frasl;2. Finally arrived about an hour before Andrew who was travelling here by train after a days work in London.
I checked in, had a walk by the river, then armed with a glass of red wine sat outside to await his arrival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 Culloden Tower</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2016cullodentower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2016cullodentower/</guid>
      <description>Friday 12th February Off to spend our 9th wedding anniversary in the Culloden Tower, built in 1736! We&amp;rsquo;re stopping off in Pontefract en route for lunch &amp;amp; a wander. Horrid place except for the stunningly beautiful All Saints church. We moved on &amp;amp; went to Richmond which is a lovely old market town &amp;amp; very hilly. We had fish &amp;amp; chips for lunch &amp;amp; a little wander, then headed for the tower to unpack the car before dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2015 Goa</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2015goa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2015goa/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 15th November Up at 4am &amp;amp; were collected by Roger to go to Gatwick. Checked in then had breakfast at Giraffe before our flight to Goa. Plane landed ½ hour early but flight still seemed endless. Queued to get visas sorted then collected cases which were waiting for us, premium certainly works from that point of view. Taxi driver sent by hotel was waiting for us, then followed 45 minutes hair raising drive to the Shanti Morada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2015 Budapest Long Weekend</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2015budapest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2015budapest/</guid>
      <description>Friday 11th September Flight to Budapest is 2½ hours &amp;amp; we are staying at the Buddha Bar Hotel. Bought Andrew some Bulgari Man aftershave in duty free, as it smells gorgeous on him. We went out for a walk and had lunch at Cafe Gerbeaud, then a look around Paprika where we bought a pretty watercolour of the Houses of Parliament on the river Danube &amp;amp; a fridge magnet. Found a C&amp;amp;A and went in as I used to like the clockhouse stuff we bought a cotton blouse &amp;amp; cotton t shirt both white the as it’s raining went back to hotel to check in as it’s after 3pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2015 Danscombe Mine</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2015danscombemine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 17:54:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2015danscombemine/</guid>
      <description>Friday 7th August Set off early for Danescombe Mine (our 22nd Landmark), stopped at lovely services in Gloucester for breakfast &amp;amp; wander around the farm shop where we bought pretty leaf mug.
Headed to Torquay &amp;amp; parked up to have a coffee and a wander around. Bought a pair of black denim shorts &amp;amp; a lovely blue dress in the BHS sales. Walked to the harbour then &amp;amp; saw a funeral parking up by the sea!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2015 Mojacar, Granada &amp; Almeria</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2015mojacar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2015mojacar/</guid>
      <description>Friday 19th June 7.40pm flight to Alicante &amp;amp; stayed at hostal Pensimar near the airport. Checked in then went to a bar close by for a drink &amp;amp; relax before bed. This is a great little hotel, friendly staff &amp;amp; open all hours for arrivals &amp;amp; departures.
Saturday 20th June After breakfast we drove to Cartagena &amp;amp; stopped at Parc Naturale for coffee &amp;amp; frittata before driving on to Mojacar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 Madeira</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2014madeira/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2014 17:45:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2014madeira/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 8th November Roger collected us at 9.15am for our Gatwick to Madeira flight. Good breakfast in Giraffe. Good flight on Norwegian airlines &amp;amp; weird landing where plane goes over Madeira then banks steeply as it turns to get to the airport at Machico. Collected Clio car &amp;amp; drove to Funchal to our apartment in the Old Town where Maria was waiting to let us in. The roads are horrendously steep, it&amp;rsquo;s like driving on a roller coaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 Mojacar</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2014mojacar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 17:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2014mojacar/</guid>
      <description>Visiting Jackie in Mojacar
Monday 8th September Up at 2.20am as couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep, arrived at Birmingham airport at 5.05am, coffee then check in. Huge queue in departures so no time for coffee, water shopping etc!!!
Arrived at Almeria, collected case &amp;amp; with Jackie about 11.20am - a good flight though we left about 40 mins late arrived only 20mins late.
Keith Jackie&amp;rsquo;s friend drove us to Mojacar where I checked in &amp;amp; changed before we went out for lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 Europe Road Trip</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2014europeroadtrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 18:02:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2014europeroadtrip/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 21st June Travelled to Dover &amp;amp; had carvery at Kittiwake pub. Drove on to ferry &amp;amp; travelled across to Dunkerque then Andrew drove from there to Bruges.
We found the apartment without too much hassle, nice but very basic, no soap, kettle etc.
Went to explore and wandered all around the old Markt area, very noisy as there was a race on. Beautiful architecture all around us, we watched the boats on the canal &amp;amp; found a restaurant with an outside eating area called Poules &amp;amp; Moules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 Cyprus</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2014cyprus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2014 17:57:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2014cyprus/</guid>
      <description>8th Feb Saturday Left home at 8,35am to drive to Luton airport for flight to Paphos in Cyprus at 11.30am.
Finally arrived in Paphos at 18.11pm 2 hrs ahead of us, so all day travel again. In a taxi to Elysium at 18.20pm.
Lovely room with a balcony.
A nice buffet with fresh salmon, asparagus &amp;amp; ok wine, went to Astoria bar for a drink &amp;amp; listened to some jazz, then bed as both worn out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2013 Vietnam for Andrew&#39;s 50th Birthday</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2013vietnam/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 18:04:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2013vietnam/</guid>
      <description>Friday 15th Nov Flew to Ha Noi (which means city inside the river) Bought Andrew a mac laptop in duty free shop. Had breakfast in Jamie&amp;rsquo;s Italian before 12 hour flight.
Saturday 16th Nov Arrived at Hanoi at 7am Vietnamese time &amp;amp; had an immediate tour as we can&amp;rsquo;t book in to the hotel till 2pm.
Nhat pronounced Nyat our tour guide &amp;amp; Hai our driver, took us around Hanoi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 Mackintosh Building</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2012mackintoshbuilding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2012mackintoshbuilding/</guid>
      <description>Friday 29th June At 5pm we drove to Morcambe after dropping Kira Katkins off at the cattery. The journey was long but uneventful, traffic &amp;amp; weather not great.
We stopped at Newcastle Under Lyme for an ok curry then continued to Morcambe arriving at The Crown at about 9.30pm to find that no one was there to let us in. Phoned &amp;amp; got the answer phone, went for a walk on the front then back to the car intending to find another hotel for the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 Las Vegas and Key West</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2012lasvegaskeywest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 07:59:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2012lasvegaskeywest/</guid>
      <description>Sat 4th February Hopefully off to Las Vegas in the morning, but we had so much snow here that we decided to book an hotel at Gatwick overnight to ensure that we are ready for the early take off in the morning.
Nick kindly drove us there, we stopped en route at Reigate for a lovely Italian dinner.
Checked in at the Hilton and Nick decided to drive home. It took him over 6 hours in the snow, plus to add insult to injury he got shunted up the rear, poor Nick!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011 Italian Cruise On The Epic Cruise Ship</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2011italiancruise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2011italiancruise/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 Sunday 26th June We flew out to Barcelona to board the Norwegian Epic cruise ship. We have State Cabin 11096 with a balcony. I unpacked &amp;amp; we settled in to explore the ship.
We ate at the Cagney&amp;rsquo;s Steakhouse restaurant onboard, steak of course which was delicious and hopefully all meals on Epic will be of this standard.
Later on we had booked tickets for the Blue Man Group at the Epic theatre, which was fabulous and so very different from any other show we have seen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011 Florida with Matt, Elliot and Nick</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2011florida/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2011florida/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 17th February  We were up really early all packed and ready to take our nephews Matt &amp;amp; Elliot on holiday to Orlando Florida. At 7.30am their Dad Jon arrived with the boys and our friend Nick, and at 8am the taxi arrived and we were off to Gatwick. We had breakfast at Frankie &amp;amp; Benny&amp;rsquo;s and a wander around duty free shops then boarded for the flight. This went well if slowly as usual, the boys were fine and soon became accustomed to flying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2010 Sri Lanka for our 3rd Wedding Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2010srilanka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2010 18:16:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2010srilanka/</guid>
      <description>Sun 7th Feb The intrepid explorers took the night flight to Colombo for our 3rd wedding anniversary holiday. Wije who is our driver and tour guide for this holiday picked us up at Katunayake Airport in Colombo and drove us to the Wallawwa hotel which is hidden away amongst trees and jungle plantation about 40 minutes from the airport. We were met by a waiter there with a fresh lime drink and ice cold towels to refresh us after our journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2008 Beckford&#39;s Tower</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2008beckfordstower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 07:20:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2008beckfordstower/</guid>
      <description>Sat 3rd May Drove to Bath from East Dulwich having spent the night with Simon &amp;amp; Clare and met Molly at last! We stopped at services for a quick lunch on the way.
Eventually found Beckford&amp;rsquo;s Tower, Fi &amp;amp; Jane arrived last night and were in town exploring.
We dropped off our luggage and walked down to the park and ride to get the bus. Had a wander around the beautiful cathedral and then the Roman Baths, walked around the terrace and took some photos of the cathedral.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2008 Thailand &amp; Laos</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2008thailandlaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 18:16:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2008thailandlaos/</guid>
      <description>Sat 12th April Andrew &amp;amp; I are off on another Gecko Travel holiday to Thailand &amp;amp; Laos, this time Nick is coming with us. Peter picked us all up &amp;amp; drove us to Heathrow.
The flight was great, although 11½ hours long, Thai Airways always get it right, even to more than edible food.
Sun 13th April We arrived at 7am Bangkok time, Mr T picked us up &amp;amp; drove us to the Viengtai hotel, singing Elvis&amp;rsquo; Can&amp;rsquo;t Help Falling In Love as he drove!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2007 Prospect Tower</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2007prospecttower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2007prospecttower/</guid>
      <description>Friday 29th June Andrew had booked another Landmark Trust holiday for my birthday weekend, this one is Prospect Tower. It’s a lovely Gothic tower which is a folly in the grounds of Belmont House near Faversham in Kent. We set off at 9.45am and reached Canterbury in time for lunch at Café de Amigos, our favourite Mexican restaurant, where we ate delectable lamb fajitas. We went for a stroll around Canterbury afterwards, stopping at the Steamer cook shop in the hopes of buying some slate place mats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2007 Dublin</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2007dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 07:27:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2007dublin/</guid>
      <description>Fri 13th April We set off to Luton Airport to fly to Dublin to spend the weekend with Susie &amp;amp; Jeremy. Flight was OK, then Susie and Jeremy collected us and drove us back to their apartment in Ballsbridge, via the city centre to show us some of the sights, the Stiffy on the Liffey included! We couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the Floozy in the Jacuzzi though.
Back at the apartment Jeremy showed us our bedroom, then we settled down in the lounge for some nachos, wine &amp;amp; a chat, catching up on what we&amp;rsquo;d all been doing since we last met.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2007 Galley Head Lighthouse</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2007galleyheadlighthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2007galleyheadlighthouse/</guid>
      <description>Fri 23rd March This is the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been on holiday without Andrew since we first got together.
The Cambridge Nutters &amp;amp; MK extras are off to Galley Head Lighthouse for our first Irish Landmark Trust holiday, booked last December. Andrew is too busy at work to make it, we&amp;rsquo;ve only been back from our honeymoon for three weeks.
Nick &amp;amp; I set off to Stansted to meet the Nutters, we have Nina, Jenny, Jennifer, Rick, Gavin, Louise, Bernie, Dave &amp;amp; Jon on this holiday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2007 Our Honeymoon</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2007ourhoneymoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2007ourhoneymoon/</guid>
      <description>Sun 11th February We set out from Simon and Clare&amp;rsquo;s new flat at about 7am having spent yesterday visiting them en route to Gatwick. It was really good to see them both as we hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen them since just after Christmas. Their new apartment in East Dulwich is really lovely. Had the usual boring drive to the airport, meandered and drank coffee till it was time to board the plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2006 The Old Vicarage</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006theoldvicarage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006theoldvicarage/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 18th November Today we set off to the Old Vicarage in Milborne Port for Andrew’s birthday weekend. We stopped at a nice little pub for lunch then drove on to Sherborne.
This is a very pretty little town, we went for a wander around the place. Lots of nice individual little shops as well as the usual chains. Stopped for coffee then went to Sherborne House for a browse around their Winter Wonderland Craft Show there is some lovely art here, pictures and sculptures in slate and glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2006 Naylands</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006naylands/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006naylands/</guid>
      <description>Friday 10th November Andrew went to work in London as usual. I packed the car and drove to Gladwin’s Farm where we are staying in the Melford suite, which is a medieval barn conversion for a few days to celebrate Andrews birthday early.
This has a four poster bed in the mezzanine floor overlooking the rest of the suite, and it&amp;rsquo;s own private jacuzzi. It&amp;rsquo;s about 2¾ hours drive and I arrived in time to unpack and relax for a while before picking Andrew up from Colchester train station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2006 Venice</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006venice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006venice/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 12th August Andrew had decided that although we had an amazing party for my 50th birthday, we need a holiday too, as he usually takes me away for my birthday. We drove to Stansted to catch the 2.15pm flight to Treviso airport just outside Venice.
On arrival we found a coach which takes you almost all the way into Venice. We boarded and were driven as far as the Grand canal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2006 Fort Clonque</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006fortclonque/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2006 18:01:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006fortclonque/</guid>
      <description>Sun 14th May We were at Nicks at 10.40am and set off to Southampton, stopping at the Bell Inn for Sunday roast. We then visited the Alms House and Hospital next door, it&amp;rsquo;s a beautiful 14th century building with stunning gardens.We really enjoyed our wander around there en route.
Reached Southampton airport in plenty of time, flight left 1&amp;frasl;2 hour early due to heavy fog in the Channel Islands. The flight was fine, and the taxi we&amp;rsquo;d booked eventually arrived to take us to Maison Bourgage for our first night in Alderney before booking in to Fort Clonque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2006 Red Sea Revisited</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006redsearevisited/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2006redsearevisited/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 23rd February I arrived at The Elms by 3.45am to make coffee &amp;amp; await Andrew’s parents Carole &amp;amp; Peter.
We set off to Stansted by to catch our 6am flight to Sharm el Sheik in Egypt, where we will be transferred to the Thomson Spirit cruise liner, our home for the next week.
It started snowing as we sat in the departure lounge and we waited while they de-iced the wings of the plane, the flight was predictably boring and 5½ hours later we landed at Sharm el Sheik and walked out into wonderful bright sunshine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2005 Prague</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2005prague/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2005prague/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 30th June I didn’t know where we were going till we checked in for our flight which took 2 hours giving me a chance to read the Prague guide book Andrew had bought for us &amp;amp; decide which parts we really wanted to explore. I love these surprise holidays.
Andrew had booked us a taxi to pick us up at the airport to take us to the hotel. We will stay at the Arcotel Teatrino a lovely Art Deco Hotel which used to be a cinema.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2005 Ischia</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2005ischia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2005ischia/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 24th May Andrew did his usual trick &amp;amp; gave me just a couple of days notice that we were off to Ischia. I love surprises!
I eventually went to bed at about midnight, &amp;amp; too excited to sleep was up again by 2.10am making coffee, we set off at 3.45am to Stansted.
Nice clear motorways, the flight took 2½ hours. We were met at Napoli airport and driven to the port, then tickets purchased, we sat looking out to sea waiting for the hydrofoil to appear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2004 Hole Cottage</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2004holecottage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2004holecottage/</guid>
      <description>Tue 31st August The intrepid explorers are off to Hole Cottage which has been at the top of my Landmark Trust places to stay list for ages, it is always booked up.
Hole Cottage is a cross-wing of a medieval timber framed house, the rest of which was pulled down in 1833, it sits in the woods by a stream.
We drove down to Canterbury for lunch at Cafe de Amigo&amp;rsquo;s, which is our favourite Mexican restaurant, and ate amazing lamb fajitas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2004 The Pineapple</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2004thepineapple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2004thepineapple/</guid>
      <description>Monday 2nd February We travelled up to the Pineapple today in Andrew’s new navy Micra, stopping only twice at motorway services on the way.
The Pineapple is a spectacular folly, built by John Murray the 4th Earl of Dunmore. He acquired the Elphinestone estate in 1754, two years before he succeeded to his title. He landscaped the garden and built the small central pavilion of just one storey with a projecting portico in the centre in 1761.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2003 Lindeth Fell Windermere</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2003lindethfellwindermere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2003lindethfellwindermere/</guid>
      <description>Friday 21st November We were up bright and early to set off to the Lake District, a romantic weekend is planned for Andrew’s birthday.
We stopped off at a pretty village pub, the Jolly Thresher in Lymm near Warrington, for an excellent lunch then motored on up the M6 to the Lindeth Fell hotel which perches above Lake Windermere. We finally arrived at dusk it was cold and very misty but the view, even so, was stunning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2003 Woodspring Priory</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2003woodspringpriory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2003woodspringpriory/</guid>
      <description>Monday 3rd February We were ready to set off for Woodspring Priory - with one problem to solve. Mischief one of our kittens was at the top of the conifer in the back garden, about 50” up wailing miserably!
A squirrel sat above her chattering, is he telling her off or threatening her? Andrew eventually talked her down and kittens safely locked in we set off. The journey down was easy, no hold ups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2002 Nerja, Granada and Barcelona</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2002nerjagranadabarcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2002nerjagranadabarcelona/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday 8th May Our flight from Luton was 2½ hours late due to fog. When we finally took off all was fine, I&amp;rsquo;d been told by the stewardess this was a new plane - only 10 days old.
We found Hertz &amp;amp; got our car a Fiat Stilo then made tracks for Nerja. Simon&amp;rsquo;s lovely girlfriend Lucy&amp;rsquo;s parents own a villa there, &amp;amp; have very kindly lent it to us for 2 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2002 Thailand and Cambodia</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2002thailandcambodia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2002thailandcambodia/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday 13th March Nick kindly took us to the airport at about 7pm. Checked in and found a really good Sushi Bar for dinner. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to get there, this is our first back packing holiday, there will be none of the usual 5* hotels and all comforts this time, it&amp;rsquo;s back to basics!
We’re going on a tour of Thailand &amp;amp; Cambodia with Gecko Travel. We&amp;rsquo;ll meet Wi our tour guide and the other 4 people in Bangkok on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2002 The Old Place of Monreith</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2002theoldplaceofmonreith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2002theoldplaceofmonreith/</guid>
      <description>Monday 18th February Andrew &amp;amp; I decided it was time for a holiday, The Old Place of Monreith was available, it also allowed dogs so we could take Sproggie.
It is a large place so we invited the Nutters along. Nick, Jennifer &amp;amp; Bernie, Gavin &amp;amp; Rick are joining us.
This Landmark Trust building was renovated in 1983 to their usual standard. Monreith or Dowies as it is also known, has a history, it used to belong to the family of Gavin Maxwell the novelist who wrote The Ring of Bright Water etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2001 Swiss Cottage and Wolveton Gatehouse</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2001swisscottagewolvetongatehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2001swisscottagewolvetongatehouse/</guid>
      <description>Friday 29th June We set off to spend my birthday at Swiss Cottage in Milton Abbot, Devon, a lovely Landmark.
We drove to Weston Super Mare, stopping for lunch, followed by a walk along the front.
We explored the Helicopter museum nearby, it is the largest in the world apparently, with 58 old helicopters dating back to the first one ever built in 1936. Andrew really enjoyed it, I did too, but found it a sad place a graveyard of lovely old helicopters, which will never fly in the sun again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2000 Lundy</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2000lundy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2000lundy/</guid>
      <description>Friday 26th May We are off on a Nutters holiday to Lundy Island, our friends accompanying us are Nina &amp;amp; Jenny with their children Tobias &amp;amp; Jack, Jennifer, Nick &amp;amp; Bernie.
Jenny has just flown back from Peru so Jennifer &amp;amp; Nina will collect her from Heathrow, then drive to Ilfracombe.
Andrew is in London &amp;amp; will be met at Taunton as he can catch the train this far from London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2000 Florida</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2000florida/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/2000florida/</guid>
      <description>Tue 1st Feb The Intrepid Explorers begin a months holiday in Florida. Our flight started at 12.45pm and arrived at 9.45pm and after all the usual hassles, we picked up our Buick Ultra and found an hotel - the Omni Rosen, a lovely suite on floor 24 with brilliant views over Orlando. A large but pretty building with a lovely fountain at the main entrance. The Buick is white, with tinted windows, cruise control, air con, CD player etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1999 San Francisco</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/1999sanfrancisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/1999sanfrancisco/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 22nd May We had a pretty good flight, landing etc. Waited for one and a half hours for our Virgin transport to the hotel and got here to find a room instead of the suite that Andrew paid for all is well. Andrew has bought Laura two Furbys for company.
We had a wander around Fullmore Street, found some really great shops and interesting fodder places. Saw some lovely Victorian houses like the Purple house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1998 St. Lucia</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/1998stlucia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/1998stlucia/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 28th June Andrew and I flew to Saint Lucia to spend my birthday in the sun, after a long flight and a very long drive through the rain forests to the other end of the island we checked in to the hotel at Rodney Bay. We were exhausted, but the nearest beach was only a couple of minutes walk. The sea was warm and the weather was wonderful, a Piton local beer for Andrew and a cocktail for me at Spinnakers beach cafe for me was deserved, and the right way to start our holiday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1997 Red Sea Cruise</title>
      <link>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/1997redseacruise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://git.andrewandlaura.com/holidays/1997redseacruise/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 4th March I was up at 3am, very excited as we leave for Egypt today. I packed my Micra &amp;amp; drove to Andrew&amp;rsquo;s house for 4.30am. then to Manchester airport, it&amp;rsquo;s a really wet windy nasty morning, but we will be in the sunshine soon!
Boarded at 9am and we are off at last the flight was late but uneventful. The plane stopped at Athens to re fuel, then flew on to Sharm El Sheikh in Egypt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>